Julius W. Becton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Prairie View A&M University, 1966-2007 (Box 97-127)
  - Target 2000 Report Card Report and related material, 1988-1994 (Box 127)
  - Transition retreat, 1990 (Box 127)
  - White House Fellows program, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 127)
- District of Columbia Public Schools, 1986-2007 (Box 127-147)
  Correspondence, speeches, notebooks and notes, government records, scrapbooks, newspaper clippings, schedules, and miscellaneous material.
  - Academic plans and student achievement, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 127)
  - Anti-Defamation League, 1996-1997 (Box 128)
  - Appointment, congratulatory letters, and related material, 1996-1997, (4 folders) (Box 128)
  - Articles (Box 128)
    - 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - 1998-2006 (Box 128)
    - Undated (Box 129)
  - Becton's account of his tenure, 1996-1998 (Box 129)
  - Boards of education (Box 129)
    - Elected board, 1993-1997 (Box 129)
    - Emergency Transitional Board of Trustees, 1996-2000, (5 folders) (Box 129)
  - Budget reports, 1996-1999, (3 folders) (Box 130)
  - Buildings, maintenance, and construction (Box 130)
    - Miscellany, 1995-1998 (Box 130)
    - Williams, Charles E., 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 130)
  - Challenges, undated (Box 130)
  - Charter schools, 1997-1998 (Box 131)
  - Chronological file (Box 131)
    - 1996 (Box 131)
    - 1997 (Box 131)
      - Jan.-Sept. (Box 131)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Box 132)
    - 1998 (Box 132)
      - Jan.-Sept., (4 folders) (Box 132)
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 133)
    - 1999-2006, (2 folders) (Box 133)
  - Council of the Great City Schools, 1998-2001 (Box 133)
  - D.C. Committee on Public Education, 1986-1998 (Box 133)
  - District of Columbia Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority (Box 133)
    - 1996-1998, Mar., (3 folders) (Box 133)
    - 1998, Apr.-1999 (Box 134)
  - Duke v. District of Columbia (Box 134)
  - Everybody Reads, 1995-1998 (Box 134)
  - Freddie Mac Foundation, "Final Report: Resource Linking Service Project," 1998 (Box 134)
  - Graduates, list, 1996-1997 (Box 134)
  - Hine Junior High School, Washington, D.C., visit, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Miscellany, 1997-2000, (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Newsletters, 1997-2003 (Box 135)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 135)
    - Communication Branch, 1996 (Box 135)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 135)
      - 1996-1997, (4 folders) (Box 135)
      - 1998-2006, (2 folders) (Box 136)
  - Notebooks and notes, 1996-1998, (3 folders) (Box 136)
  - Other school systems (Box 137)
    - Chicago., Ill., (4 folders) (Box 137)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-2002 (Box 137)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1996 (Box 137)
    - New York, N.Y., 1998-1999 (Box 137)
    - School networks, 1996-2000 (Box 138)
  - Parents United for the D.C. Public Schools, 1994-2003, (2 folders) (Box 138)
  - Personnel, 1994-1997, (3 folders) (Box 138)
  - Press releases, 1997-2000 (Box 138)
  - Principals (Box 138)
    - "Confidential Directory of Principals," 1997 (Box 138)
    - "Confidential Directory of Principals," 1997 (Box 139)
    - Miscellany, 1997-1998 (Box 139)
  - Printed matter, 1997-2003 (Box 139)
  - Public Education Partnership Fund, 2003 (Box 139)
  - Retirement, 1998, (3 folders) (Box 139)
  - Schedules and appointments, 1989-1997 (Box 139)
  - Schedules and appointments, 1989-1997, (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Speeches (Box 140)
    - 1995 (Box 140)
    - 1996 (Box 140)
      - July-Nov. (Box 140)
      - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - 1997 (Box 141)
      - Jan.-Feb., (5 folders) (Box 141)
      - Mar.-May, (5 folders) (Box 142)
      - June, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 142, Box 143)
      - July-Oct., (7 folders) (Box 143)
      - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 144)
      - Circa (Box 144)
      - Circa, (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - 1998 (Box 145)
      - Jan.-June, (5 folders) (Box 145)
      - Nov. (Box 146)
    - 2000-2007, (2 folders) (Box 146)
  - Summer conference for administrators, 1992-1997 (Box 146)
  - Task forces, 1996-1997 (Box 146)
  - Teacher recruitment presentation, 1998 (Box 146)
  - TQM Educational Consultants, undated, (2 folders) (Box 146)
  - TQM Educational Consultants, undated (Box 147)
  - Transportation Division, 1997-1999 (Box 147)
  - Truancy, 1998 (Box 147)
  - Department of Education, 1999 (Box 147)
- Organizations, 1943-2008 (Box 147-172)
  Printed matter, trip itineraries, correspondence, reports, articles, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alpha-numerically by name of organization, and thereunder alphabetically by type of material.
  - 555th Parachute Infantry Association, 1979-1995 (Box 147)
  - 761st Tank Battalion and Allied Veterans Association, 1996 (Box 147)
  - American Battle Monuments Commission (Box 147)
    - Cemeteries, 2002-2004, (2 folders) (Box 147)
    - Chronological file (Box 147)
      - 2001-2003 (Box 147)
      - 2004-2005, undated, (3 folders) (Box 148)
    - Commissioners, 2001 (Box 148)
    - European trip, 2004 (Box 148)
    - Orientation notebook, 2001 (Box 148)
    - Printed matter, 2000-2001 (Box 148)
    - World War II Memorial, Washington, D.C. (Box 148)
      - Chairman's Advisory Group, 2001-2002 (Box 148)
      - Chairman's Advisory Group, 2001-2002 (Box 149)
      - Commissioners' meeting, 2002 (Box 149)
      - Dedication ceremony, 2004 (Box 149)
      - Design committee, 2001 (Box 149)
      - Inscriptions, 2001-2002, (3 folders) (Box 149)
      - Miscellany, 2001-2003 (Box 150)
      - National World War II Reunion, 2004 (Box 150)
      - Packet, 2002 (Box 150)
      - Photo booklet and photographs, 2002-2003 (Box 150)
      - Printed matter, 2003-2004 (Box 150)
      - Tribute to a Nation, calendar, 2004 See Oversize (Box 150)
  - American Coastal Industries, 1989 (Box 150)
  - American Public University System (Box 150)
    - 2007, (2 folders) (Box 150)
    - 2008 (Box 151)
  - Association of the United States Army (Box 151)
    - George Catlett Marshall Medal (Box 151)
      - Emails, 2007 (Box 151)
      - Guest lists, 2007 (Box 151)
      - Miscellany, 1987, 2004, 2007 (Box 151)
      - Printed matter, 1988- 2008, (2 folders) (Box 151)
      - Newsletters, 2007 (Box 151)
      - Speeches, 2007 (Box 151)
    - Kursk, Russia, battlefield tour (Box 151)
      - Articles, 1985, 1993 (Box 151)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1996, undated, (4 folders) (Box 151)
      - German and Soviet archival material, 1943 (Box 152)
      - "The Improbable Journey," Becton's account, 1996 (Box 152)
      - Miscellany, 1996 (Box 152)
      - Notes and itineraries, 1996 (Box 152)
    - Miscellany, 1973, 1997, 2006-2008 (Box 152)
    - Printed matter (Box 152)
      - 1981, 1996-2007, (3 folders) (Box 152)
      - 2008 (Box 153)
    - Quadrennial Defense Review, 1997 (Box 153)
    - "Voice for the Army, Support for the Soldier," presentation, undated (Box 153)
  - Atlantic Council, 1981, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 153)
  - Blewitt Foundation, 2007 (Box 153)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Box 153)
    - American Military Culture in the 21st Century, 1998 (Box 153)
      - Chronological file (Box 153)
        - 1998 (Box 153)
        - 1999 (Box 154)
      - Conference packet, 1998 (Box 154)
      - Executive summary, 2000 (Box 154)
    - Junior Reserve Officers Training Corps (Box 154)
      - Miscellany, 1998-1998 (Box 154)
      - Printed matter, 1998-1999 (Box 154)
    - Military Assistance to Inner Cities project, 1996 (Box 154)
    - Professional Military Education project (Box 155)
      - Loose leaf, 1996 (Box 155)
      - Miscellany, 1989-1996 (Box 155)
    - Spector, Ronald H., "The Higher Military Schools Between the Wars: Their Contribution to Professional Development, Doctrine, and Strategy 1919-1940," 1995 (Box 155)
    - Terrorism Task Force (Box 155)
      - Chronological file (Box 155)
        - 1986-1995, (3 folders) (Box 155)
        - 1996-1998, undated, (3 folders) (Box 156)
    - "Global Organized Crime," 1994 (Box 156)
  - The Citadel, Charleston, S.C. (Box 156)
    - MacCauley, Alexander Stevens, "Black, White, and Gray: the Desegregation of the Citadel, 1963-1973," masters thesis, 1998 (Box 156)
    - Miscellany, 1999-2000 (Box 156)
  - Council of 100: A Black Republican Organization, 1986-1988 (Box 156)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower Society, 1976, 1986 See also Oversize (Box 156)
  - Eisenhower World Affairs Institute, 2002 (Box 156)
  - Emergency Preparedness Review Committee, City and County of Philadelphia, 2005-2006, (4 folders) (Box 157)
  - Ends of the Earth Club, 2003 (Box 157)
  - Florida A&M University, Tallahassee, Fla. (Box 157)
    - Annual report, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 157)
    - Miscellany, 2001-2002 (Box 157)
    - Office of the Inspector General, 2002 (Box 158)
  - Forestville Military Academy, Forestville, Md., 2004 (Box 158)
  - Fort Leavenworth Memorial Hall Association, 1998-1999 (Box 158)
  - General Dynamics Corp. (Box 158)
    - Audit Committee (Box 158)
      - Miscellany, 2000-2003 (Box 158)
      - Printed matter, 1999-2002, (3 folders) (Box 158)
    - Director's data books, 1997-1999, (3 folders) (Box 159)
    - General Dynamics Corp. v. United States, 1998-2001 (Box 159)
    - Miscellany, 1997-2000 (Box 159)
    - Printed matter, 1999 (Box 160)
  - George C. Marshall Foundation (Box 160)
    - Board of Trustees, 1998-1999 (Box 160)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 160)
    - Dinners, 1995-1997 (Box 160)
    - Hall of Honor, Lexington, Va., 1995 (Box 160)
    - "Marshall at State," 1995 (Box 160)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 160)
    - ROTC Award Seminar and ROTC Youth Conference, 1995-2000 (Box 160)
  - Hay Group, 1985, undated (Box 161)
  - Illinois Tool Works, 1992-1996, undated, (4 folders) (Box 161)
  - Indianhead Association, 1976-1985 (Box 161)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, Washington, D. C., 1984 (Box 161)
  - Library of Congress, Veterans History Project (Box 161)
    - 2001 (Box 161)
    - 2001 (Box 162)
    - 2002-2006, (3 folders) (Box 162)
  - Marine Spill Response Corp., 1991-1993, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 162)
  - Military Officers Association of America, 2005-2008 (Box 163)
  - Military Order of the Carabao, 1995 (Box 163)
  - Miscellaneous, A-H, 1978-2006, (4 folders) (Box 163)
  - Mosher Institute for International Policy Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 163)
  - Muhlenberg College, Allentown, Pa., 1987-1989 (Box 163)
  - National Academy of Public Administration, 1988 (Box 163)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1982-1985, 2000 (Box 164)
  - National Association of Uniformed Services, 1969-1971, undated, (3 folders) (Box 164)
  - National Cathedral Association, 1998 (Box 164)
  - National Minority Military Museum Association Foundation, 1978 (Box 164)
  - National Museum of the United States Army, 2008 (Box 164)
  - Neighbors, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1968 (Box 164)
  - Network for Instructional TV (Box 164)
    - 1998
    - 1999-2007, undated, (6 folders) (Box 165)
  - Ninth and Tenth Cavalry Association, 1972-1995 (Box 165)
  - Ninth Infantry (Manchu) Association, 1984-1991 (Box 166)
  - Noncommissioned Officers Association, 1985 (Box 166)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1954 (Box 166)
  - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1982-1983 (Box 166)
  - Retired Officers Assocation, 1983-1988, (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - The Rocks (Box 166)
    - Army staff briefing, undated (Box 166)
    - Becton interview, undated (Box 166)
    - Chronological file (Box 166)
      - 1973-1998, (2 folders) (Box 166)
      - 1999-2009, undated, (3 folders) (Box 167)
    - Printed matter, 1989-2007 (Box 167)
  - Sino-American Aviation Heritage Foundation, circa 1990 (Box 167)
  - Stonehouse Investors, 1995-1996 (Box 167)
  - Southwest Association of Buffalo Soldiers, 2006-2007 (Box 167)
  - Toastmasters International, 1956-1964 (Box 167)
  - U.S.-Korea 2000 Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 167)
  - United Service Organization (Box 168)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (4 folders) (Box 168)
    - Printed matter, 1987-1990 (Box 168)
    - Becton biographical information and membership lists, 1986-1987 (Box 168)
  - United States Armor Association, 1987-2000 (Box 168)
  - United States Army Corps of Engineers, 1998 (Box 168)
  - United States Department of Veterans Affairs (Box 168)
    - Miscellany, 1988-1989 (Box 168)
    - Printed matter, 1988-2002, (3 folders) (Box 169)
  - United States Military Academy, West Point, N.Y., 2007 (Box 169)
  - University of Georgia System Board of Regents (Box 169)
    - Chronological file, 1995, undated, (4 folders) (Box 169)
    - Notes, 1995 (Box 170)
    - Printed matter, 1994-1995 (Box 170)
    - Savannah State College, 1995 (Box 170)
  - Valley Forge Military Academy and Junior College, Wayne, Pa. (Box 170)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1989, 1998-2007, (4 folders) (Box 170)
    - Miscellany, 1978-1982, 1990, 2004 (Box 171)
    - Trustee meetings, 1988 (Box 171)
  - Wackenhut Corp. (Box 171)
    - Chronological file (Box 171)
      - 1995-1999, (3 folders) (Box 171)
      - 2000 (Box 171)
        - Jan.-May (Box 171)
        - May-Dec. (Box 172)
      - 2001-2002, undated, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - Presentations, 2000 (Box 172)
- Speeches and Writings, 1945-2007 (Box 172-189)
  Drafts, correspondence, research files, and background material relating to Becton's autobiography; speeches; books by others; and speech idea files.
  Arranged alphabetically into Becton's autobiography, book review by Becton, books by others, and speeches by Becton.
  - Becton: Autobiography of a Soldier and Public Servant (Box 172)
    - Background material (Box 172)
      - 1988-2007, (3 folders) (Box 172)
      - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2007, (4 folders) (Box 173)
    - Drafts, editing copies, and interviews with Julius W. and Louise Becton (Box 173)
      - 1995 (Box 173)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 173)
      - 2002 (Box 173)
      - 2002, (4 folders) (Box 174)
      - 2003 (Box 174)
      - 2004, (2 folders) (Box 174)
      - Circa 2004, (4 folders) (Box 175)
      - 2005 (Box 175)
      - 2007, (2 folders) (Box 175)
      - Undated (Box 176)
        - Additions (Box 176)
        - "By the Grace of God", (3 folders) (Box 176)
        - "By the Grace of God", (2 folders) (Box 177)
        - Untitled (Box 177)
          - Acknowledgment, dedication, forward, and prologue (Box 177)
          - Chapters 1-11 (Box 177)
          - Chapters 12-17 (Box 177)
          - Chapters 18-21 (Box 178)
          - Chapters 22-25 (Box 178)
    - Illustrations, undated (Box 178)
    - List of abbreviations, undated (Box 178)
  - Book reviews by Becton, 1984, 1993 (Box 178)
  - Books by others (Box 178)
    - Anderson, Trezzvant W., Come Out Fighting, 1945 (Box 178)
    - Black Panthers Wrapped in Cold Steel: Pictorial History of the 761st Tank Battalion in World War II, undated (Box 178)
    - Bowers, William T., Black Soldier, White Army: the 24th Infantry Regiment in Korea, 1995, (5 folders) (Box 179)
    - "Doctor of Defense," synopsis, undated (Box 179)
    - Maloney, Gerard A., A Heck of a Ride, undated (Box 179)
    - Manual on army small unit leadership, undated (Box 179)
    - Miskel, James F., Disaster Response and Homeland Security: What Works, What Doesn't, 2006 (Box 180)
    - Posey, Edward L., The U.S. Army's First, Last, and Only All-Black Rangers: The 2d Ranger Infantry Company (Airborne) in the Korean War, 1950-1951 (Box 180)
      - 2004 (Box 180)
        - May-June, (2 folders) (Box 180)
        - July-Aug. (Box 181)
    - Wagner, Robert E. (Box 181)
      - "Old Cavalry Notes," 2001 (Box 181)
      - "The Warrior Manual for Mounted Combat," 1989 (Box 181)
  - Speech ideas (Box 181)
    - Miscellany (Box 181)
      - 1954, 1964-2003, (5 folders) (Box 181)
      - 2004-2007, undated, (5 folders) (Box 182)
    - Speeches by others (Box 182)
      - circa 1960-1969, (2 folders)
      - 1972-2008, undated, (7 folders) (Box 183)
  - Speeches by Becton (Box 184)
    - 1969-1993, (8 folders) (Box 184)
    - 1994-1998, (7 folders) (Box 185)
    - 1999-2000, (7 folders) (Box 186)
    - 2000-2008, (6 folders) (Box 187)
    - Undated, (3 folders) (Box 188)
    - Fragments, undated, (2 folders) (Box 188)
    - Indexed speeches (Box 188)
      - 1977-1983, (3 folders) (Box 188)
      - 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 189)
- Subject File, 1780-2008 (Box 189-196)
  Family papers, biographical material, topical files, regional histories, newspapers and newspaper clippings, and real estate records.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - 24th Infantry Regiment (Box 189)
    - Carlisle, David K., 1995-1996 (Box 189)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 189)
  - 42nd Armored Infantry Battalion, reunion, 1987-1988, undated (Box 189)
  - African American generals and flag officers (Box 189)
    - Hamlet, James, 2000-2001 (Box 189)
    - Jones, Otis D., 1979 (Box 189)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1989, 1994, 2007 (Box 189)
    - Nabors, Robert L., 1999-2002 (Box 190)
    - Powell, Colin L, 1992-2002 (Box 190)
    - Robinson, Roscoe, 1995, 2000-2003 (Box 190)
    - Waller, Calvin A. H., 1994-1997 (Box 190)
  - African American history (Box 190)
    - Calendar, 2008 (Box 190)
    - Military (Box 190)
      - 364th, 366th, and 372nd Infantry Regiments, 1999-2001 (Box 190)
      - Black Americans in Defense of the Nation, Department of Defense, 1982 (Box 190)
      - Buffalo soldier campaigns in the American West, maps, undated (Box 191)
      - Golden Buffalo Presents Black Military History, 1770-1975 calendar, 1989-1990 See Oversize (Box 191)
      - "The Medal of Honor and African Americans in the United States Army during World War II," presented to the United States Army Military Awards Branch, 1995 (Box 191)
      - Miscellany, 1918, 1964, 1973-1976, 1993-1998, 2007 (Box 191)
      - U.S. Army World War II Asiatic-Pacific Theater, map, 1995 (Box 191)
    - Miscellany, 1983, 1998, 2005 (Box 191)
  - Alaska cruise, 1997 (Box 191)
  - Becton, Julius W. (Box 191)
    - Biographies, 1972, 1982-1983, 1992-2003, undated (Box 191)
    - Diploma, Lower Merion High School, Ardmore, Pa., 1944, 1944 (Box 192)
    - Miscellany, 2006, undated (Box 192)
    - Passports, 1977-1998 (Box 192)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 192)
    - Senior Officer Oral History program, United States Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa. (Box 192)
      - Miscellany, 1995-1996 (Box 192)
      - Interviews, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 192)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 2000 (Box 192)
  - Cain, Jonathan, Revolutionary War soldier, certificate of service, 1780 (Box 192)
  - CDC 1604 computer, 1965 (Box 193)
  - Daniel, Bill, governor of Texas, 1987, 2000 (Box 193)
  - Dixon, Eddie, sculpture, undated (Box 193)
  - F-108 (aircraft), bomb racks, undated (Box 193)
  - Family papers (Box 193)
    - Alexander, Gladys, estate, 1996-2001, undated (Box 193)
    - Miscellany, 1956-2008, undated See also Oversize, (3 folders) (Box 193)
  - Hayfield Hawks News Magazine, Hayfield Secondary School, Alexandria, Va., 2008 (Box 194)
  - Hong Kong, China, Vietnam, trip, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 194)
  - Horton, W. C., 2006 (Box 194)
  - Korean War (1950-1953), 1999-2000, 2008, undated (Box 194)
  - Lower Merion Township, Pa. (Box 194)
    - Bryn Mawr, 1944, 1969, 1976-1979 (Box 194)
    - Lower Merion High School, Ardmore, Pa. (Box 195)
      - Class of 1944, (3 folders) (Box 195)
      - Miscellany, 1942, 1969-2005 (Box 195)
    - Miscellany, 1978, 1998-2007 (Box 195)
  - Metropolitan Dialog on Civic Leadership with People of Faith, 1999 (Box 196)
  - Mexico, undated (Box 196)
  - Patton family, 2002-2008 (Box 196)
  - Real estate (Box 196)
    - Miscellany, 1964-1973, 2006 (Box 196)
    - Valley Ridge East, Springfield, Va., 1970-1984, 1992-1903 (Box 196)
  - Tschannerl, Gautama, 1995-1999 (Box 196)
  - Versace, Humbert Roque, 1999 (Box 196)
- Miscellany, 1961-2008 (Box 196-198)
  Awards, appointment calendars, cartoons and caricatures, obituaries, biographical sketches of others, photographs, slides, resumes, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Appointment calendar, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 196)
  - Awards and certificates, 1969-2006 (Box 197)
  - Cartoons and caricatures, undated See also Oversize (Box 197)
  - Inscriptions, undated (Box 197)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1961-2008, undated, (2 folders) (Box 197)
  - Obituaries and biographical sketches, other people, 1985-2008 (Box 197)
  - Photographs, undated See also Oversize (Box 197)
  - Printed matter (Box 197)
    - 1969, 1981, 1988, 1995, 2001-2003, (4 folders)
    - 2005-2007 (Box 198)
  - Resumes, other people, 1980-2002, undated, (2 folders) (Box 198)
  - Slides (Box 198)
    - Becton, Louise, birthday, undated (Box 198)
    - Israel, 1977 (Box 198)
    - Miscellany, undated, (2 folders) (Box 198)
    - Vietnam and Southeast Asia, circa 1967-1968, (2 folders) (Box 198)
- National Security Classified Information, 1954-1991 (Box NATO 1)
  Documents containing security information removed from the collection.
  Arranged and described according to the series from which the items were removed.
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization
      - Chronological file
        - Isamy, terms of reference for intrastructure committees, 1954 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - A. Synadino, senior civil emergency planning committee present terms of reference of the SCEPC, 1969 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - The Norwegian Concept of Total Defense Summary of Civilian Support to the Armed Forces. Presented at the NATO Defense Planning Symposium, 1989 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Presentations given at the Senior Civil Emergency Planning Symposium, 1989 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Agenda, Senior Civil Emergency Planning Committee, 1990 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Secretary General to Permanent Representatives, 1990 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Agenda, Senior Civil Emergency Planning committee, 1991 training programme, 1990 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - L. E. Davies to Director, Private Office, meeting of the Deputy Secretary General with the New Select Group, 1990 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Cable, Paris 37197, regarding visit of NATO Civil Emergency Planning Committee to Paris, 1989 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Index, report of the New Select Group, undated (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Senior Civil Emergency Planning Committee New Select Group, discussion paper, undated (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - ASG for Infrastructure, logistics, and Civil Emergency Planning to ASG for Defense Planning and Policy, input to the spring coordination report, 1990 (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
        - Les Plans D'Urgency au Grand-Duche de Luxembourg, undated (Container 84) (Box NATO 1)
      - Loose leafs
        - Cable, US-NATO 04806, regarding background information for General Becton's use..., 1989 (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - Cable, US-NATO 06599 regarding DPC ministerial meeting.…, 1989 (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - USSR domestic outlook, undated (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - "Working Paper," undated (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - Warsaw Pact reform, undated (Box NATO 1)
        - Cable, US-NATO 00530, regarding broadening NATO-Japan contacts..., 1990 (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - Partial cable, US-NATO 000632, undated (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
        - John J. Policasto to Becton et al, regarding New Select Group Meeting, 1990 (Container 85) (Box NATO 1)
- Oversize, 1969-1994 (Box OV 1-OV 11)
  Scrapbooks, calendars, posters, photographs, cartoons, and awards.
  Arranged and described according to the series, container, and files from which the material was removed.
  - Army Career (Box OV 1)